HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/003 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- LSO Financial Assistance - 1988 Local 54 Atlantic City, N.J. Strike Bene. - Local 100 New York, N.Y. LSO Subsidy Roll #22A Master (Reel 59)
  - Local 99 - Duluth, MN - LSO, 12 (Reel 59)
  - Financial Assistance Files, 1988; 13 (Reel 59)
  - Local 100 - New York, NY - LSO Subsidy, 14 (Reel 59)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 150 Syracuse N.Y. - Local 369 Albert Lea, Min., Strike Benefits roll #23A Master (Reel 60)
  - Local 150 - Syracuse, NY - Hotel Syracuse Strike, 1 (Reel 60)
  - Local 122 - Milwaukee, WI, 1988; 2 (Reel 60)
  - Local 165 - Las Vegas, NV - LSO, 1988; 3 (Reel 60)
  - Local 206 - Winnipeg, Man., Canada - LSO Subsidy, 4 (Reel 60)
  - Local 217 - New Haven, CT - Organizing Subsidy, 5 (Reel 60)
  - Local 226 - Las Vegas, NV, 1988; 6 (Reel 60)
  - Local 261 - Ottawa, Ontario, Canada - Lockout at Four Seasons Hotel, 7 (Reel 60)
  - Local 270 - Myrtle Beach, SC - LSO, 1988; 8 (Reel 60)
  - Local 272 - Ottawa, Ontario, Canada - Organizing Subsidy Proposition #2361, 9 (Reel 60)
  - Local 274 - Philadelphia, PA - LSO, 1988; 10 (Reel 60)
  - Local 301 - Philadelphia, PA - Organizing Subsidy, 1988; 11 (Reel 60)
  - Local 312 - Kalispell, Montana - LSO Subsidy, 12 (Reel 60)
  - Local 355 - Miami Castle Resort Strike, 13 (Reel 60)
  - Local 369 - Albert Lea, MN - Strike Benefits, 1988; 14 (Reel 60)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 427 Missoula Mt. - Local 9 Portland, Oreg. Roll #24A Master (Reel 61)
  - Local 427 - Missoula, MT - LSO, 1988; 1 (Reel 61)
  - Local 442 - Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada - Proposition #2174, 2 (Reel 61)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL - LSO, 1988; 3 (Reel 61)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL, 1988; 4 (Reel 61)
  - Local 457 - Butte, MT - Organizing Subsidy Proposition #1882, 5 (Reel 61)
  - Local 483 - Monterey, CA - Organizing Subsidy GEB, 1986; 6 (Reel 61)
  - Local 471 - Albany, NY - LSO File, 1988; 7 (Reel 61)
  - Local 604 - Peterborough, Ontario, Canada - Trent Inn Lockout, 8 (Reel 61)
  - Local 610 - P.R. Revolving Fund, 9 (Reel 61)
  - Local 610 - Revolving Fund, 1987-1988; 10 (Reel 61)
  - Local 610 - Virgin Islands - Proposition #1881-H, 11 (Reel 61)
  - Local 662 - Hailfax, N.S., Canada - LSO, 1988; 12 (Reel 61)
  - Local 767 - LSO, 13 (Reel 61)
  - Financial Assistance, 1989; 14 (Reel 61)
  - Local 1 - Chicago, IL - LSO Pat Montes De OCA, 15 (Reel 61)
  - Local 4 - Buffalo, NY - Organizing Subsidy Proposition #1294-C, 16 (Reel 61)
  - Local 5 - Honolulu, HI - Strike at Pleasant Hawaiian Hotel Proposition #2889, 17 (Reel 61)
  - Local 6 - New York, NY - Strike at Tavern on the Green Proposition #2883, 18 (Reel 61)
  - Local 7 - Baltimore, MD - LSO Proposition 2214, Proposition 2213A, 1989; 19 (Reel 61)
  - Local 9 - Portland, OE - LSO Subsidy Proposition #2624, 20 (Reel 61)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 10 Organizing LSO - Local 40 LSO roll #25A Master (Reel 62)
  - Local 10 - Cleveland, OH - LSO, 1 (Reel 62)
  - Local 11 - Carnegie Deli Strike, 1989; 2 (Reel 62)
  - Local 12 - Cincinnati, OH - LSO Reports, 3 (Reel 62)
  - Local 12 - Cincinnati, OH - Attorney Fees, 4 (Reel 62)
  - Local 15 - LSO - Mary F. Jarrett Southern Illinois, 5 (Reel 62)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing Subsidy, 6 (Reel 62)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing Subsidy Proposition #1673-B, 7 (Reel 62)
  - Local 20 - Springfield, IL - LSO Subsidy Report Proposition #3109, 8 (Reel 62)
  - Local 25 - Washington, D.C., 9 (Reel 62)
  - Local 26 - Boston, MA, 10 (Reel 62)
  - Local 28 - Oakland, CA - Corinne Comer, Emil Abate, 11 (Reel 62)
  - Local 30 - San Diego, CA - Local Special Organizer Proposition #1207-B, 12 (Reel 62)
  - Local 40 - RC Branch - Proposition #1972-B, 1988-1989; 13 (Reel 62)
  - Local 40 - Burnaby, BC, Canada - Royal Canadian Branch #57, 1989; 14 (Reel 62)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, B.C., Canada - LSO, 15 (Reel 62)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, B.C., Canada - Versa Services WCB Caf Teria, 16 (Reel 62)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 40 Van Couver BC, Canada Versa Services - Local 100 New York, N.Y. 1989 Stephanie Bonfonte (Reel 63)
  - Local 40 - Sacramento, CA - Organizing Subsidy, 1 (Reel 63)
  - Local 49 - Sacramento, CA - LSO Subsidy, 1989; 2 (Reel 63)
  - Local 62 - Fresno, CA - LSO Subsidy, 1989; 3 (Reel 63)
  - Local 70 - Dayton, OH - Proposition #2421, 2421-A, 2421-B, 4 (Reel 63)
  - Local 75 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada - Organizing Subsidy, 5 (Reel 63)
  - Local 75 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada - Strike at Cara Oper. Pearson, 6 (Reel 63)
  - Financial Assistance Files, 1989; 7 (Reel 63)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - Marg. Johnson LSO, 8 (Reel 63)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - Kathy Campbell LSO, 9 (Reel 63)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - Organizing Subsidy, 10 (Reel 63)
  - Local 88 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 11 (Reel 63)
  - Local 99 - Duluth, MN - LSO Subsidy, 12 (Reel 63)
  - Local 100 - New York, NY - Stephanie Bonfonte, 1989; 13 (Reel 63)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 122 Milwaukee, WI. - Local 355 Miami, Fl. LSO roll #27A Master (Reel 64)
  - Local 122 - Milwaukee, WI - San Gallo, 1989; 1 (Reel 64)
  - Local 150 - Syracuse, NY - LSO, 1989; 2 (Reel 64)
  - Local 150 - Syracuse, NY - Hotel Syracuse, 3 (Reel 64)
  - Local 150 - Syracuse Hotel Strike, 4 (Reel 64)
  - Local 165 - Las Vegas, NV - LSO Subsidy, 5 (Reel 64)
  - Local 206 - Winnipeg, Man., Canada - Union Central Strike, 6 (Reel 64)
  - Local 206 - Winnipeg, Man., Canada - Gary Whalen LSO, 7 (Reel 64)
  - Local 217 - New Haven, CT - Organizing Subsidy Proposition #2196-P, 8 (Reel 64)
  - Local 226 Memorandum, 9 (Reel 64)
  - Local 226 - LSO Reports Pearlman, 10 (Reel 64)
  - Local 226 - LSO Reports Roxann Tynam, 11 (Reel 64)
  - Local 226 - LSO Reports Steve Jandwicz, 12 (Reel 64)
  - Local 226 LSO Reports Daughtery, 13 (Reel 64)
  - Local 251 - Houston, TX - LSO Reports, 14 (Reel 64)
  - Local 261 - Ottawa, Ontario, Canada - LSO Subsidy, 15 (Reel 64)
  - Local 270 - Myrtle Beach, SC, 16 (Reel 64)
  - Local 272 - Ottawa, Ontario, Canada - LSO, 1989; 17 (Reel 64)
  - Local 274 - Philadelphia, PA - Tom Muma LSO, 18 (Reel 64)
  - Local 301 - Philadelphia, PA - Organizing Subsidy, 1989; 19 (Reel 64)
  - Local 355 - Miami, FL - LSO, 20 (Reel 64)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 355 Miami, Fl., Doral Hotel & Country Club - Local 6 N.Y. Club 101 roll #28A Master (Reel 65)
  - Local 355 - Miami, FL - Doral Hotel & Doral Country Club, 1 (Reel 65)
  - Local 355 - Miami, FL - Castle Resort Strike, 2 (Reel 65)
  - Local 355 - Miami, FL - Castle Resort, 3 (Reel 65)
  - Local 400 - Spokane, WA - LSO Subsidy, 4 (Reel 65)
  - Financial Assistance Files, 1989; 5 (Reel 65)
  - Local 427 - Missoula, MT - LSO Anna Sochocky and Lisa Sargeson, 6 (Reel 65)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL - Sam Cassata and Joe Spano, 7 (Reel 65)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL - LSO Weekly Reports Proposition #1350E, 1350F, 1350G, 8 (Reel 65)
  - Local 471 - Albany, NY - LSO Peter Jensen, 9 (Reel 65)
  - Local 483 - Monterey, CA - Organizing Subsidy GEB, 1986; 10 (Reel 65)
  - Local 531 - Pasadena, CA - Lisa Blanco, 11 (Reel 65)
  - Local 533 - Helena, MT - LSO Subsidy, 12 (Reel 65)
  - Local 535 - San Bernadino, CA, 13 (Reel 65)
  - Local 610 - San Juan, Puerto Rico - Organizing, 14 (Reel 65)
  - Local 681 - Long Beach, CA - Local Special Organizers, 15 (Reel 65)
  - Local 737 - Orlando, FL - Organizing Subsidy, 16 (Reel 65)
  - Local 767 - Regina Sask. Canada - LSO Reports Tom Rees Jr., 17 (Reel 65)
  - Local 1 - Chicago, IL - LSO Subsidy, 1990; 18 (Reel 65)
  - Local 4 - Formerly 66 - Buffalo, NY, 1990; 19 (Reel 65)
  - Local 5 - Honolulu Hotel Strike 1990, 20 (Reel 65)
  - Local 6 - NY Club 101 - Restaurant Marketing Assistance, 21 (Reel 65)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 7 Baltimore, MD. - Local 24 Detroit, MI roll #29A Master (Reel 66)
  - Local 7 - Baltimore, MD, 1 (Reel 66)
  - Local 8 - Seattle, WA - Local Special Organizer Subsidy, 2 (Reel 66)
  - Local 9 - Portland, OE, 3 (Reel 66)
  - Local 10 - Cleveland, OH - Organizing, 4 (Reel 66)
  - Local 12 - Cincinnati, OH - LSO Subsidy, 5 (Reel 66)
  - Local 15 - Southern Illinois, 6 (Reel 66)
  - Local 16 - Peoria, IL - LSO Subsidy, 7 (Reel 66)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Proposition #1673-C, 8 (Reel 66)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing #1673-B file 2, 9 (Reel 66)
  - Local 20 - Springfield, IL - LSO #3109, 10 (Reel 66)
  - Local 21 - Detroit, MI - LSO Proposition #3155, 3155A, 1989-1990; 11 (Reel 66)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 25 Washington D.C. - Local 84 Toledo, OH Marg. Johnson roll #30A Master (Reel 67)
  - Local 25 - Washington, D.C. - Proposition #2726, 1 (Reel 67)
  - Local #26 - Boston, MA, 2 (Reel 67)
  - Local 28 - Oakland, CA, 3 (Reel 67)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, B.C., Canada - #2437-C, 4 (Reel 67)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, B.C., Canada - Royal Canadian #26 Lockout, 5 (Reel 67)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, B.C., Canada - Domco Food/King Ed Campus, 6 (Reel 67)
  - Local 47 - Edmonton, Alberta, Canada - LSO Subsidy, 7 (Reel 67)
  - Local 62 - Fresno, Ca - LSO Proposition #3553, 8 (Reel 67)
  - Local 73 - Thunder Bay, Ontario, Canada - Don Campbell, 9 (Reel 67)
  - Local 70 - Dayton, OH - LSO, 1990; 10 (Reel 67)
  - Local 75 - Toronto, Canada, 1990; 11 (Reel 67)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - Kathy Campbell, 12 (Reel 67)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - Marg. Johnson, 13 (Reel 67)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 86 Reno, NV. - Local 274 Phila., PA. LSO Thomas Mumay roll #31A Master (Reel 68)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - Proposition #2986, 1990; 1 (Reel 68)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - Organizing Proposition #2986-Q, 1990; 2 (Reel 68)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - #2986-R (7/17/90), 1990; 3 (Reel 68)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - Organizing Subsidy #2986N-O, 1990; 4 (Reel 68)
  - Local 99 - Duluth, MN - LSO, 1990; 5 (Reel 68)
  - Local 100 - New York, NY - Stephanie Bonfonte, 6 (Reel 68)
  - Local 100 - New York, NY - Ross O'Country, 7 (Reel 68)
  - Local 100 - New York, NY - 101 Things to Eat, 8 (Reel 68)
  - local 104 - Tampa, FL - Proposition #3640, 1990; 9 (Reel 68)
  - Local 122 - Milwaukee, WI, 10 (Reel 68)
  - Local 150 - Syracuse, NY - LSO, 11 (Reel 68)
  - Local 165 - Las Vegas, NV, 12 (Reel 68)
  - Local 206 - Winnipeg, Man., Canada - LSO, 1990; 13 (Reel 68)
  - Local 217 - New Haven, CT - Organizing, 14 (Reel 68)
  - Local 251 - Houston, TX, 15 (Reel 68)
  - Local 261 - Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 16 (Reel 68)
  - Local 261 School Board, 17 (Reel 68)
  - Local 270 - Myrtle Beach, SC - David Richardson, 18 (Reel 68)
  - Local 270 - Myrtle Beach, SC, 19 (Reel 68)
  - Local 274 - Philadelphia, PA - LSO Thomas Mumau, 20 (Reel 68)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 274 LSO Liza Beautz - Local 767 Regina Sask. Canada roll #32A Master (Reel 69)
  - Local 274 - Lso Liza Beatuz, 1 (Reel 69)
  - Local 274 - Philadelphia, PA - Kink Rexford, 2 (Reel 69)
  - Local 301 - Philadelphia, PA - Proposition #1462-C,D,E, 3 (Reel 69)
  - Local 312 - Kalispell, MT - Proposition #1861 Fordon Hall Machel Smith, 4 (Reel 69)
  - Local 355 - Miami, FL - A Lynn Scott, 5 (Reel 69)
  - Local 355 - Miami, FL - Holiday Inn Collins Ave, 6 (Reel 69)
  - Local 400 - Spokane, WA - Local Special Organizer, 7 (Reel 69)
  - Local 427 - Missoula, MT - Lisa Sorenson, Becky Fascione, 8 (Reel 69)
  - Local 442 - Niagara Falls, Canada, 9 (Reel 69)
  - Local 442 - Niagara Falls, Ontario, Canada, 10 (Reel 69)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL, 11 (Reel 69)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, Il - Sam Cassata, 12 (Reel 69)
  - Local 471 - Albany, NY - Peter Jensen, 13 (Reel 69)
  - Local 483 Organizing, 14 (Reel 69)
  - Local 483 - Montery, CA, 15 (Reel 69)
  - Local 531 - Pasadena, CA, 16 (Reel 69)
  - Helena, MT - Mitchell P. Crilly, 17 (Reel 69)
  - Local 610 - San Juan, Puerto Rico, 18 (Reel 69)
  - Local 681 - Long Beach, CA, 19 (Reel 69)
  - Local 737 - Orlando, FL, 20 (Reel 69)
  - Local 767 - Regina Sask. Canada, 21 (Reel 69)